{
    "subject": "resource/Simcere_Pharmaceutical",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_drug",
    "human_readable": "Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drug.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.969106137752533,
            "question": "What industry is Simcere Pharmaceutical involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8307856321334839,
            "question": "What type of products does Simcere Pharmaceutical produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216761946678162,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing Simcere Pharmaceutical in its industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7829129099845886,
            "question": "Is Simcere Pharmaceutical a local or global company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7254315614700317,
            "question": "Where is Simcere Pharmaceutical headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6261458396911621,
            "question": "Does Simcere Pharmaceutical have any partnerships with other companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6241748332977295,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a product made by Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025691032409668,
            "question": "What is the overall mission or vision of Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5609532594680786,
            "question": "What are the main areas of focus for Simcere Pharmaceutical's research and development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5587133765220642,
            "question": "How does Simcere Pharmaceutical contribute to public health?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drug.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8100_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main areas of focus for Simcere Pharmaceutical's research and development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8100_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall mission or vision of Simcere Pharmaceutical?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8100_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a product made by Simcere Pharmaceutical?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8100_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8100_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that the context information provided contains text from various documents, and one of them (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8100/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt) explicitly states that Simcere Pharmaceutical Group is a \"leading pharmaceutical company specializing in the development, manufacturing, and marketing of branded generic and proprietary pharmaceuticals in China\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Simcere Pharmaceutical Group as a leading pharmaceutical company involved in the development, manufacturing, and marketing of various types of pharmaceuticals. This information supports the statement that Simcere Pharmaceutical is in the industry of pharmaceutical drugs."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}